And I'm gonna show you some simple home remedies that you could do at home.
So basically you don't have to go back to the dry cleaner, cause I
think you know most people. Yes.
There you go. All right, so where are we starting? So we're going to start
off with the first. By the way, there are three different
stain groups. To 95% of all stains come
from three different groups. The first group is from the Earth. That's anything from
the Earth, like fruit juices, colas, teas, red wines.
Okay. The second is from the body, which is protein. Anything live matter
from the body. All the icky stuff, like blood, milk,
perspiration. Okay. And the third is all oil matter.
That's mineral, vegetable, and petroleum oils. That can be from hair gels to cooking oils,
greases, et cetera. Let's test makeup. Exactly. The first category
is earth based, so we're going to take some coffee,
okay. Which is everyone's got a coffee stain. And we're going to stain it on
this item right here. But what we make to make the solution at
home is we're going to take 2oz of dishwashing detergent, a degreaser,
pour it in, okay. 2oz of vinegar, one piece of
white vinegar, and go ahead. And 2oz of water.
Okay. Simple enough. And we're just going to mix it up.
Okay. And what you always do before
you use this on anything, you always want to test the
solution in an inconspicuous area of the garment
to make sure that the color doesn't bleed. Because you
can go right on, the color starts bleeding,
this flap on the inside of the ship. And you always want to
with an earth based stain, you always want to just rinse it with cold
water just to see if it's going to come out because it's fresh.
We're going to take the formula and we're going to tamp it right
on top of the stain. You can see it, right? And it passes, like,
right through. It passes right through. Wow. You can see
that. That's awesome. There it goes.
Okay, number two, we're going to the protein based
thing. So we chose since
we're in the kitchen here, we chose meat, juice,
blood. Okay. So we take two tablespoons of water, a teaspoon
of ammonia, a teaspoon of peroxide,
hydrogen peroxide. Hydrogen peroxide, and a teaspoon of detergent.
Okay, again. All right. When I see ingredients
there you go. This is good. Okay.
So what we're going to do is pour it on. Yeah.
And by the way, one of the other tips is if you ever have excess
amount of the solution or
no excess amount of stain, just take it off. Take it off with a
round object, a spoon or something. Got you. There you go.
And just tamp. Beautiful. Look at that.
The last squad. Let me get this right. Last group,
I'm going to just take a this is the makeup, the oil based. Yeah.
This is the lady stuff or just the oil based stuff.
So we're going to use this wherever
you want or you want to do it. Now, we always start
with an ounce of degreaser and an
ounce of a tablespoon or an ounce of water. Now,
to make this stronger, if you need to,
we add acetone. Okay,
it works. But as long as you don't
have any acetate fabric right, then you can use that.
It will definitely melt it, you'll see? Okay. There you go. So now
let me grab one of these.
Can I spoon it on, please? Keep a spoon it on. She knows how it
this is good French service for your same. There you
go. Okay. And there you
can see it coming off. Wow. And that was bright pink lipstick.
If you just let it sit there, sometimes it works. Over time,
it's getting through. So you can't always be in a rush to remove stains,
and then you wash it afterwards. There's a mild
detergent and clorox to a safety bleach. Oh,
cool. Yeah.
Thank you.